

Patrik Patal

145 Eden St., St Michael Village Ma-a, Davao City, Davao Del Sur $\,/\,$ awesomepatrik22@gmail.com +639561793440

Summary

A full-stack developer specialized at the backend development but can do front-end with the basic fundamentals. Stacks used Laravel, CodeIgniter, .Net Framework, VueJS, JQuery, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS. Programming languages used PHP, Javascript, Visual Basic, C#, MySQL, MSSQL, HTML, CSS.

Can provide client services by details based on the requirements. Able to work with a team composing different roles accepting the role being assigned and also can work individually.

Education

Bachelor Science in Information Technology

Holy Cross of Davao College, Davao City, Davao Del Sur 11/2012

Skills

- · Laravel
- Vuejs
- · SQL Database
- · SSH Ubuntu Linux
- PHP
- CSS
- Tailwind

- · Codeigniter
- · JQuery
- · AWS Platforms
- · JavaScript
- HTML
- Bootstrap

Experience

LeanCurve

Full Stack Developer, Copenhagen

Stack: Laravel, PHP, Javascript, JQuery, MYSQL, AWS Services, VueJS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Serverless Laravel Vapor.

12/2020 - 04/2022

Ideahub IT Solutions Inc

Backend Developer, Davao City, Davao Del Sur Stack: Laravel, PHP, Javascript, JQuery, MYSQL, AWS Services, VueJS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap 05/2018 - 12/2020

JTC Group of Companies

MIS / Systems Developer, Davao City, Davao Del Sur Stack: Visual Basic 6, .NET Framework, MYSQL 11/2015 - 05/2018

Davao Central Warehouse Club Inc.

Systems Developer, Davao City, Davao Del Sur

Stack: Visual Basic 6, MySQL

01/2013 - 01/2015

Languages Filipino English